Luke will be making
me a
custom
bookshelf next year
, but since neither of
us have
much
time for such tasks right now,
I
decided to temporarily buy some bookshelves
.  These are only temporary for now
, I
need a place to put my books,
because
they are all
piled up by the windows
, it's
really quite a
mess
.  So,
I
hope these will help keep the books more organized
.
Fortunately
, these bookshelves are
very easy to assemble.    To be
honest
,
I'm
not that skilled at making things or reading instructions.  So, so far
I have been able to
complete both
.
Now let
's try something else
.  But I hope you
enjoy it
, because
I'm
sure you won't see me making anything again,
because it's
not my job.
I finally got the
bookshelves
ready, and
now it's
a big job to bring all my books down from the treehouse upstairs and arrange them here.
So, that's the
next step.
Books,
books,
books.    There are
some
.  I thought all my
books
would fill all these shelves
,
but actually
three and a half shelves
are empty, which is
good
because I
work at a bookstore
so I get to bring home a lot of
free
books
.  Most of the books I have behind me are
second-
hand or
free,
because
I get copies of
Advanced
Readers for working at the bookstore
.
That's one of the benefits of working there.
You
will receive books that are not yet available to the public early
so that you can
read and review them
.  However,
I also have a lot of
new
books
,
because I
like to encourage new authors and
I also
recently became a
writer
.
So, I want to share with you some books that I am
currently
reading, have
recently
read, or am
interested in reading
.  I recently reread 'The Apothecary', one of
my
favorite
books from my childhood
.
This is a story about the
magical power of plants
and two
children
.  It feels very
cozy
and is about nature, the
wonders of nature
.
Although not strictly in a realistic sense, it is a
very, very
fun
book.
That's why I
recently
reread it.
I haven't
read it yet,
but I'm very excited to read 'Oak, Ash,
and Thorn'
.
This was gifted to me by a
viewer
,
so
thank you if you are one.
Its cover is very
beautiful.
It features small,
magical creatures
,
which is why
I liked it so much
.  I
recently reread the book 'Never
More',
which was one of my
favorite
books from my childhood
.  I
always say this book is like '
Harry Potter'
, but
it
has a heroine and a
greater
emphasis on magical animals
, which I
like.
I'm
rereading this as the second book has just been released
.  I also recently reread 'The
Wolf and the
Whale'
,
which is also a
favorite
book of mine.    To be
honest,
I didn't really like the ending
, but
up until the last 50 pages, this was
one of my favorite books.
That's why, even though I
think the ending would have been better if it had been different,
I would still
read it again and
enjoy it.
Yes, many people ask me
what kind of
books I
read
, and I
say that I read many types of books.  I
have a very sensitive psyche,
so I
can't stand scary things,
especially if they're
dark about supernatural forces
.  That's why,
I don't
like those kinds of books that much, but I
try to read all kinds of books
.  For me, reading
is an
escape and
it's very good for my mental
health
because I can
immerse myself in another world.
I
love fantasy, these
books
take me to another world and
help me imagine what the world could be like.
Some of my favorite
books are the ones
I
read as a child, and I
still have them
.
One of them is 'The
Girl's Book
of Flower
Fairies', whose
spine is
completely
broken
.
You
can see how chaotically I wrote this at the age of seven.
I've read this
book so
many times that I could
even
take it to the forest
.  I would keep this with me to remember anything I saw there
.
This is another book I have had since I was a child.
This is
another
field guide about fantastical creatures.    As
a child, I used to
take this book with me when I went into the forest,
so that I could
accurately record anything I found
.  I also have 'Tasha
Tutor's
Book of
Fairy Tales'
, a
book that is
very
hard to find outside now.  This is a very
old book.    If
you don't
know who Tasha Tutor is,
she was a
famous
and
popular
children's
author a few decades ago.  She is no longer with
us
.  But I
also had the opportunity to write her a letter when I was very young
.  She was unable to write back to me because
she was ill at the time
.
But when she was sick in bed
, she wrote
me a letter back with the help of her son
.
She
died shortly after that.
I definitely
consider it one of the most special letters in my house and a treasure,
because
I still
keep that letter written by her son, which
she
helped me with.
That would be really, really
good.    If
it stays that way, I
still have
some space on my shelf.
So, I
thought I'd go to the bookstore and get some more new books that I could read.
I've already
read all the books behind me,
so I
definitely want
to get some new books
and
look at them in the future to
decide which ones will be of good use to others
.  Yes, I repeat
,
I wrote a
book
.
If you are interested,
I will give the details below.  Sending
my love to all of you
.  I hope you
like it
.  It's definitely going to be
very, very
fun
.  And
yes, if there are any books you
like,
always
let us know in the comments below.